[{"answer": "But no, a star is born.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 12, "question": "I'm sure you don't mind being called a star then Lupita?", "qSentId": 11}, {"answer": "It is snowing from New Jersey to Alabama, and just on the eastern side of the snow it's freezing rain and sleet.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "Tell me what's going on?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "Piers, what a difference two week makes.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "What's going on?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Wow, I've been in Kenya, you know, basking in the sun and getting ready for this.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Where have you been?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Getting ready, preparing for the onslaught?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "But no, a star is born.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "I'm sure you don't mind being called the star then Lupita?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "CQUEEN: Beyond.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Was it like a real moment?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "or you didn't have a clue?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Yeah, and, you know, Patsey -- whenever Patsey speaks it's from a place of extremist.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Did you gave your everything?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "I was on my way out of my apartment in New Haven.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "So, where, where you when you got the call from this man that was going to change your life?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Were you emotional?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "Did you cry?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "This girl's amazing, right?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "I raised my hand up and I just closed my eyes and cried and said thank you, thank you, thank you.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "And when the horse went Lupita Nyong'o, what were you doing in that moment?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "Well, you know, well Brad Pitt is one of those names that everyone's heard but I guess he just could place it (ph), you know, what was important was whether he knew him personally or not.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "No, but I'm just so grateful that it has.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Did you think it would have quite the impact of resonance that it's had?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "It's wonderful while it goes, right?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Good to see you, buddy.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "I'll talk to the man who's seen it all before, Arsenio Hall is live and in the house, great man how are you?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "It doesn't feel right but that's because he's my friend.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "That he's going?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "Yeah, I mean he's ...", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Is it just because he was number one for so long?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Well, Johnny Carson is the best.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Who's being the best?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "You know, he kind of taught my generation how to do it and as I said that, I started thinking Steve Allen was brilliant.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Can anyone ever beat the Carson grip on the American audience or simply because he was the only one really for a long period doing it?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "If you're going to put money on which Jimmy to win the new war who would be the winner?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "I call you that when we're off the air.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "Do you say it on air on your show?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "As a comedian...", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Should it just be decommissioned as a word if you take the assumption which is the correct one that is inherently offensive?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "ALL: Well, it's just...", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "... was fantastic, right?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think so.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "... and he was welcoming the father, right?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "I don't know how you would feel, right?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "By the way, there's a GN who anonymously said this guy won't get dropped.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "How do they know?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Jason Brown -- Chicago's Jason Brown.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Does he know you had a connection to one of Olympics -- America's Olympics athletes?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Yeah, for sure.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "You extended (ph) and then you have to go wait?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "A text?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "So you're sitting with your phone?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Do you sit there as a sports fan really enjoying it?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "This is when you know you're not enjoying it when you start looking for the countries like with two guys and you laugh, \"What he got was a bow and arrow.\"", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Why can't they all just come out together?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "You've been mocking people, isn't it?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Let's talk about Black history month.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Want to go skating later?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Well, didn't Morgan Freeman make a statement about this?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Well...", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Is he right?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "That's possible.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "... but has it drawn out more racism having the first black American president for example?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "I, you know, I don't experience racism.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "When you walk around in America now, do you yourself experience any over racism because people know who you are?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Did you follow what happened to Samuel L. Jackson?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "And that's why you said it right?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "Late night, baby.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Well, now, what was your wish?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "What are you proudest of all your accomplishments?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "No, I'm not confident to win a Winter Olympic gold medal, I'm confident to maybe, you know, make my country proud of me.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "Mexico has never won a Winter Olympic gold medal, are you confident?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Have you pick some of this everyone talking about his eyes?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "No, I mean, it's a strange story but it kind of develops like that.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "There really is no (ph) into your talent, is there Prince Hubertus?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "I do, I do.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 660, "question": "Oh, you do?", "qSentId": 659}, {"answer": "Courage, integrity, you know, anybody who was abandoned, I mean, to you as a father is the best domain crutch (ph) in a man's life and stay for a reason because you know if that ever comes down to it, you got your own father who lean up against...", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "What impact do that have on you?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "Oh, he loved it.", "docId": "140212pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "So what did you thought what your father made of you being Oscar nominee?", "qSentId": 682}]